[{"answer": "I'm great, Piers.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Governor, how are you?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Somebody tweeted me in the middle of last night's show.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, you know I explained.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "How do you react to that?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Well, look, first of all, you cannot deny that there are still people out of work.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "None of this is very good for the president, is it?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "I'm very well, thank you.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Have you recovered?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "None.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Any regrets?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "ELCH: Particularly -- I was surprised when you think about the fact that they've called Governor Romney a felon.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "But were you surprised by the ferocity of the attacks on you?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Here's the problem I see for you, Jack, going forward is if Mitt Romney becomes president, every single time the job figure is announced and it's gone down, i.e., it's good news for him, every Democrat will jump up and say, Jack Welch says this is complete rubbish.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "This is 2,000 people calling up and saying, are you working?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Auto is as strong.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "That is green shoot for the housing industry, right?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Well, we did --", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Do you want to take a chance on that?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "They put it into the wrong place with the wrong headline.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "If that's what gets Obama home, wasn't that one op-ed piece a disaster?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "I -- no, hold it.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Is it down to a question mark?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Hello, Piers.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Donald, how are you?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Well, there's a massive difference.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "But what is the difference between Mitt Romney's refusal to release his tax returns and the president not being inclined to release his college records?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Well, I'll tell you, as far as I'm concerned, I think, and I told this to Mitt, if you -- if he release I'd like to do a swap.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "What's stopping him -- in this new spirit of transparency that you want to see, what is to stop your friend Mitt just saying, you know what, I know there are doubts, people still -- see the offshore records, here it is going back 12 years?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Well, the only reason he would do it --", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Piers, why wouldn't he do it?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think --", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Well, why wouldn't he take it up?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "I don't think he would, is my point.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "But Piers, why wouldn't he take it up?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "Memorably awful.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Well, the point is it was memorable, right?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "I think it's probably a rehabilitation of Clint Eastwood as much as it is an endorsement of Mitt Romney.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What do you think of Clint Eastwood and his apparent flip- flopping?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "I don't see -- you are right.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Isn't he?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "That's not what he said.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Right, you would like Mitt Romney to stand up tomorrow and say that God intends rapes to happen, would you?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I don't think we should misquote him.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Am I wrong here?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Right, and I think there's a part -- this becomes very personal.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Charles Blow, am I misrepresenting when he says that basically he's saying, look, you know, women who get raped and have babies, it's all God's will?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I personally believe that there should be an exception in the case of rape.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Katie Pavlich, why is it not a woman's decision in the most most appalling circumstance of being raped, that she decides without any fear of censure from anybody else in America -- she decides what she does?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "What I would say is this idea that Goldman is relieved or find nothing in the book, I think this is part of this Wall Street mentality.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Are there any things that you regret about all this?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "The biggest misconception right now in terms of the financial crisis, -- Dodd-Frank was a bill that was passed almost two years ago.", "docId": "121024pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Do you see any changes since this has all blown up?", "qSentId": 611}]